[Support Home](https://www.namesilo.com/Support) :: [Policies](https://www.namesilo.com/Support/Policies) :: [Terms and Conditions](https://www.namesilo.com/Support/Terms-and-Conditions) :: Privacy Policy

* * *

Privacy Policy
--------------

NameSilo Respects Your Privacy
------------------------------

This privacy policy covers how we collect and use the personal information you provide on the NameSilo sites that link to this privacy policy. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update that information. Personal information is information about you that can be used, directly or indirectly, to identify you (name, phone number, address, date of birth, email addresses, etc.). Information that does not allow identification of you, is not considered personal information. Except as described in this privacy policy, we will not disclose personal information to others without your authorization.

Information Collection and Use  

---------------------------------

### Tracking Technologies

Our Site uses cookies and tracking technologies to identify your account(s) so that you can securely utilize our services. The cookies are associated with your account, however, they utilize a session ID so that your internal account ID is never exposed. Furthermore, we utilize industry best practices to prevent session/cookie hijacking to ensure our use of cookies does not expose your personal information. You can disable cookies in your web browser; however, doing so may prevent you from utilizing most services on our site. An alternative to disabling cookies is to configure your web browser to delete all cookies upon closing the browser - this way you can utilize all of NameSilo's services, while only storing/using cookies while they are necessary.

While using our site, our affiliates and/or analytics or service providers may use cookies and scripts to analyze web requests and site traffic trends, including users' movements around our site for purposes of gathering demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive data from these providers on an individual or aggregated basis which helps us better understand web site traffic trends; however, no personal information in our possession is relayed to any of these providers as part of this process.

### Forms

As is customary for all providers in NameSilo's business, our site uses forms to collect personal information (including your name, address, telephone number, and email address) so you can place orders, manage your services, and request information and support. We may also request proof of identification, financial information, or other forms of information necessary to provide the services that you request.  
  
Any information you transmit to us via forms on our site, or give us in any other way, including through email, our API, phone, or via contacting our support team will be stored. This information may be used for purposes of contacting you regarding your use of our services. You may update personal information stored or request not to be contacted by us - see below under "Updating Your Information"  

### Protocol Data

We gather certain information that is naturally transmitted as part of handling standard Internet protocols, such as HTTPS. We use this information, gathered as a result of your use of our services, via the Internet, to help personalize our site, diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer our site. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or click-stream data. We also gather broad demographic information from this data to help us improve our site and service offerings.

### WHOIS Data

Most domain registrations require publishing contact-related information in WHOIS ([https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WHOIS](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/WHOIS)). With most registrars this process, by default, involves transmitting your personal information to the registries responsible for the top-level domains in your account(s). NameSilo is different - by default, we do not transmit your personal information to domain registries thereby preventing disclosure of personal information in WHOIS. Our WHOIS privacy service ([https://www.namesilo.com/Support/WHOIS-Privacy](https://www.namesilo.com/Support/WHOIS-Privacy)) is free and is enabled by default. It is still possible for you to transmit and publish your personal information in WHOIS by explicitly disabling WHOIS privacy on a per domain or account-level basis; however, you have to explicitly request that this be done via our site.

A few country code top-level domain registries have policies preventing us from protecting your personal information from being disclosed in public WHOIS - those ccTLDs are listed here: [https://www.namesilo.com/Support/WHOIS-Privacy](https://www.namesilo.com/Support/WHOIS-Privacy)

If you choose to opt out of our free WHOIS privacy service, please review the privacy portion (where available) of the Registry Policies for the top-level domain in which you wish to or have registered a domain name to better understand how your WHOIS data is utilized by the individual registry. Also, please note that when you disable WHOIS privacy, your personal information will become publically available. This means that anyone can download/store/copy/distribute your personal information; even if you enable WHOIS privacy later on.

### Security

We use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control. When you enter sensitive information on our web site forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using Transport Layer Security (TLS).  

We follow accepted industry standards to protect the personal information transferred to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of information storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us: [https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us](https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us).

### Google Analytics  

We utilize "Google Analytics" ([https://www.google.com/analytics/](https://www.google.com/analytics/)) to collect information about the use of our site, such as how often users visit, what pages they visit, and their click-path through our site. Google Analytics does not collect personal information as part of this process.  
  
Google Analytics sets a permanent cookie in your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site. Use of this cookie is restricted to Google Inc. Information generated gathered as a result of this process will stored by Google on servers in the United States.  
  
We use the information received from Google Analytics only to improve our site and the services that we offer. We do not combine the information collected by Google with any personal information.  
  
Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to our site is governed by Google's privacy policy: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to our site by deleting the Google Analytics cookie, or following the technique(s) described above in the Tracking Technologies section.  

### Data Retention and Access  

Upon request we will provide you with a confirmation about whether we hold, or process on behalf of a third party, any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by contacting us using any of the methods below:

* Access your account on our site: [https://www.namesilo.com/login](https://www.namesilo.com/login)  
    
* You may send us mail at our physical address listed here: [https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us](https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us)
* You may send an email to [\[email protected\]](https://www.namesilo.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

To deactivate your account, please login and submit an authenticated contact form here: [https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us](https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us)

NameSilo will respond to requests for access or to modify or deactivate personal information within thirty (30) days.

### Do Not Track Browser Setting  

Some browsers allow you to automatically transmit a "Do Not Track" signal to web sites that you visit. There is no established consensus as to what "Do Not Track" means in this context. We do not currently consider this signal from browsers when offering services on our site. To learn more about "Do Not Track", you can visit: [https://allaboutdnt.com/](https://allaboutdnt.com/)

### What Happens to Your Personal Information if You Cancel Your NameSilo Account

If your NameSilo account is cancelled all of your personal information is placed in "deactivated" status in our databases. Even though your account may be deactivated, that does not mean your personal information has been deleted from our databases. We will retain and use your personal information as necessary in order to meet our legal obligations.  

### Updating Your Information

After logging into your account on our site, you may update your account information or opt-out of receiving communications from us at any time (Account Home > "account maintenance" and/or Account Home > "contact manager").  
  
Please recognize that, where your personal information is necessary for the provisioning your requested services, or for the operation of our systems, the collection, use and disclosure of personal information is required and you cannot opt-out or delete the information without terminating your services/products.

### Transfer of Data Abroad

If you are using our site from a country other than the country in which our servers are located, any of your communications with us may result in the transfer of information across international borders. You acknowledge and agree that in order to service our customers' requests, inquiries and/or issues, our support operations, including support provided via phone, chat, and email, are spread around the globe. Therefore, when you place a call, chat, or email from your country, it is possible that the call, chat, or email will be supported by NameSilo personnel in another country (including, for example, one outside of the EEA), and that any information provided will be transferred to that country. Regardless of any data transfer abroad, your information will be processed in accordance with this privacy policy. By using this site, calling, emailing, or chatting with our customer service personnel, or otherwise communicating electronically with us, you consent to such transfers.

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including without limitation subpoenas), to protect our property and rights or the property and rights of a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we consider to be illegal or unethical. We will also share your information as required to comply with ICANN's regulations, rules and policies.  
  
To the extent we are legally permitted to do so, we will take reasonable steps to notify you in the event that we are required to provide your personal information to third parties as part of legal process.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy policy and any other places we deem appropriate, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

### Contacting Us  

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, or the practices of this site, please contact us at the address listed here: [https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us](https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us)  

Privacy Shield
--------------

NameSilo supports the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. NameSilo is committed to subjecting all personal information received from European Union (EU) member countries to the Privacy Shield Framework’s applicable Principles. You can learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework by [visiting the U.S. Department of Commerce's Privacy Shield](https://www.privacyshield.gov/).  
  
NameSilo is responsible for the processing of the personal information we receive, under the Privacy Shield Framework, and any subsequent transfers of said information to any third party acting as an agent on behalf of NameSilo. NameSilo complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal information from EU member countries, including any provisions governing onward transfer liability.  
  
In certain situations, NameSilo may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities of appropriate venue, including to meet law enforcement or national security requirements.

If you have a personal information use concern that we have not addressed to your satisfaction, please contact us at [https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us](https://www.namesilo.com/contact-us) We take your privacy and security seriously and will work to resolve concerns.

Per the [Privacy Shield web site](https://www.privacyshield.gov/), in certain scenarios, you may invoke binding arbitration if other dispute resolution mechanisms have failed to resolve personal information privacy matters.

* [
    
    cheap](javascript:;)
    
    Find the cheapest domains on the web with NameSilo!
    
    No hidden fees. No upsells. No bait and switch... Just cheap domains!
    
    You don't have to qualify by ordering other services, placing minimum orders, or worry about fees getting tacked on before purchase. The price you see is the price you pay!

* [
    
    easy](javascript:;)
    
    Just want to get your domain and get on with life?
    
    At NameSilo, we believe registering and renewing should be _fast..._
    
    We will never bombard you with offers for services you don't want and are already getting elsewhere. Just select your domain names, fill out a 1-page form, and get on with your life!

* [
    
    secure](javascript:;)
    
    Secure your domain name assets and get peace of mind with Domain Defender
    
    Don't be another victim of malicious domain name attacks and changes!
    
    Unauthorized changes to your domain names could result in serious damage to your business. Prevent simple mistakes and keep hackers from compromising your valuable assets.

* [
    
    tools](javascript:;)
    
    Who said "cheaper" meant sacrificing quality?
    
    We put powerful tools in your hands to manage your domains.
    
    Take advantage of our best-in-class domain management tools. Easily categorize, locate and modify your domain settings one-by-one or in bulk. We also offer a secure API for common domain management tasks.

© 2009 - 2024 NameSilo, LLC  
All Rights Reserved
